https://optibike.com/privacy-policy/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to usOptibike LLC is located at: Optibike LLC 41404 Stewart Mesa Rd Paonia 81428 CO , US 3034430932It is Optibike LLC’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to
optibike.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “optibike.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of service posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms of service.ContentsClick below to jump to any section of this privacy policyWebsite VisitorsPersonally-Identifying InformationSecurityOptibike LLC uses Google AdWords for remarketingAggregated StatisticsCookiesE-commerceContact Information & Credit1. Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Optibike LLC collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Optibike LLC’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Optibike LLC’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Optibike LLC may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Optibike LLC also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://optibike.com blog posts. Optibike LLC only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.Back to table of contents2. Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Optibike LLC’s websites choose to interact with Optibike LLC in ways that require Optibike LLC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Optibike LLC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who leave a comment at https://optibike.com to provide a username and email address.Back to table of contents3. SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Back to table of contents4. Optibike LLC uses Google AdWords for remarketingOptibike LLC uses the remarketing services to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.Back to table of contents5. Aggregated StatisticsOptibike LLC may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Optibike LLC may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Optibike LLC does not disclose your personally-identifying information.Back to table of contents6. CookiesTo enrich and perfect your online experience, Optibike LLC uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Optibike LLC uses cookies to help Optibike LLC identify and track visitors, their usage of https://optibike.com, and their website access preferences. Optibike LLC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Optibike LLC’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Optibike LLC’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Optibike LLC’s use of cookies.Back to table of contents7. E-commerceThose who engage in transactions with Optibike LLC – by purchasing Optibike LLC’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Optibike LLC collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Optibike LLC. Optibike LLC does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Back to table of contents8. Contact Information & CreditThis privacy policy was created at privacyterms.io privacy policy generator. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.Back to table of contents
The Electric Bike Book | Free Download
Get My Free Book
HomeContact OptibikeMedia | Press KitPrivacy PolicyMy AccountSitemap
© 2020 Optibike.
All Rights Reserved.
HomeBrowse the BikesCompare All ModelsElite Series | from $11,900Optibike R15C Full CarbonOptibike R8C Full CarbonOptibikes for WomenPro Series | from $6,400Optibike Essex ‘Fit Freedom’Urban Series | from $3,495Rocky Mountain CommuterPioneer Allroad LimitedPioneer AllroadFinancingAccessoriesUsed and RefurbishedDeal of The WeekOptibike AdvantagesWarranty45 Day GuaranteeOptibike Design & TechnologyTech: Optibike MotorLong Range TouringClimb any HillElectric Bike BasicsWhat is a Rohloff Hub?Velodrome RacingReviews & CompareReviews and TestimonialsTrustpilot ReviewsCompare Stromer ST5 with Optibike R8CE-Bike BenefitsFree Electric Bike Book7 Mistakes when Buying an E-Bike3 Myths of Electric BikesThe Best Couples Guide to Electric BikesBorn to Be WildChoose the Perfect E-BikeBenefits of an Electric BikeElectric Bikes vs MopedsElectric Bikes for WomenRide an Electric Bike for FreeServiceManuals and GuidesPartsContactAbout UsOur StoryOptibike 10 Year AnniversaryMedia | Press KitMy AccountNewsGet in touch (303) 443-0932
Optibike NewsletterDon't miss out on our sales and discounts!
Subscribe
All Set!
